- ConversationTopicId: 1427_0104_TalkTo_CultMother
  PlayerPrompt: "@1427_0104_TalkTo_CultMother_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@1427_0104_TalkTo_CultMother_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 1427_0101_TalkTo_Cultist01
  PlayerPrompt: "@1427_0101_TalkTo_Cultist01_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@1427_0101_TalkTo_Cultist01_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 1427_0101_TalkTo_Cultist02
  PlayerPrompt: "@1427_0101_TalkTo_Cultist02_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@1427_0101_TalkTo_Cultist02_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 1427_0101_TalkTo_Cultist03
  PlayerPrompt: "@1427_0101_TalkTo_Cultist03_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@1427_0101_TalkTo_Cultist03_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 1427_0101_TalkTo_CultOfficer
  PlayerPrompt: "@1427_0101_TalkTo_CultOfficer_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@1427_0101_TalkTo_CultOfficer_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 1427_0102_TalkTo_CultOfficer_Pilgrimmage
  PlayerPrompt: "@1427_0102_TalkTo_CultOfficer_Pilgrimmage_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@1427_0102_TalkTo_CultOfficer_Pilgrimmage_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 1427_0109_TalkTo_CultOfficer_Gold
  PlayerPrompt: "@1427_0109_TalkTo_CultOfficer_Gold_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@1427_0104_Oath_Complete_b"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 1427_0102_TalkTo_Oath
  PlayerPrompt: "@1427_0102_TalkTo_Oath_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@1427_0102_TalkTo_Oath_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 1427_0102_TalkTo_Daughter_Umbrage
  PlayerPrompt: "@1427_0102_TalkTo_Daughter_Umbrage_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@1427_0102_TalkTo_Daughter_Umbrage_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 1430_CultLeader_HighSage
  PlayerPrompt: "@1430_CultLeader_HighSage_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@1430_CultLeader_HighSage_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 1430_CultLeader_AboutCult
  PlayerPrompt: "@1430_CultLeader_AboutCult_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@1430_CultLeader_AboutCult_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 1430_CultLeader_AboutMask
  PlayerPrompt: "@1430_CultLeader_AboutMask_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@1430_CultLeader_AboutMask_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 1434_0104_TalkTo_Dryad
  PlayerPrompt: "@1434_0104_TalkTo_Dryad_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@1434_0104_TalkTo_Dryad_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 1424_Fisher_ExplainHotspots
  PlayerPrompt: "@0223_Fisher_ExplainHotspots_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0223_Fisher_ExplainHotspots_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 14_Antara_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@14_Antara_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@14_Antara_T1_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 14_Antara_T2
  PlayerPrompt: "@14_Antara_T2_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@14_Antara_T2_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 14_Milosh_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@14_Milosh_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@14_Milosh_T1_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 14_Andeolus_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@14_Andeolus_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@14_Andeolus_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 14_Joan_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@14_Joan_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@14_Joan_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 14_Tello_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@14_Tello_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@14_Tello_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 14_Babak_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@14_Babak_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@14_Babak_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 14_Zhao_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@14_Zhao_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@14_Zhao_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 14_Yadira_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@14_Yadira_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@14_Yadira_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 14_Zorzi_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@14_Zorzi_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@14_Zorzi_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 14_Faramarz_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@14_Faramarz_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@14_Faramarz_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 14_Yazdan_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@14_Yazdan_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@14_Yazdan_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 14_Eva_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@14_Eva_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@14_Eva_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 14_Gwen_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@14_Gwen_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@14_Gwen_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 14_Roger_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@14_Roger_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@14_Roger_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 14_Walter_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@14_Walter_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@14_Walter_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 14_Wolcott_T1
  PlayerPrompt: "@14_Wolcott_T1_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@14_Wolcott_T1_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
